<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- New XML document created with EditiX XML Editor (http://www.editix.com) at Thu Jan 22 15:29:06 CST 2015 --><messages>
	<message>
		<id>0</id>
		<nextMessage>1</nextMessage>
		<text>So there you are, the Golden Finger Hero! Our world was attacked by evil monsters, please save us! TUTORIAL: Hold Z to move to the next the dialog or open the achievement window. Press Z to attack.</text>
		<type>selection</type>
		<avatar>1</avatar>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>1</id>
		<nextMessage>2</nextMessage>
		<text>"A strange energy wave is coming out of my finger! What the fuck is going on?!"</text>
		<type>reply</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>2</id>
		<nextMessage>3</nextMessage>
		<text>What are you waiting for? Is this the first time you've ever played a tutorial? As the most talented developer of this world, I have invented the simplest and most elegant gameplay - using only one key!</text>
		<type>selection</type>
		<avatar>1</avatar>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>3</id>
		<nextMessage>4</nextMessage>
		<text>"I got this game for it's 18+ rating, but this developer is starting to creep me out..."</text>
		<type>reply</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>4</id>
		<nextMessage>5</nextMessage>
		<text>As you're incredibly dense, let me tell you how to play, again. This game only needs your Z key, so even Stephen Hawking can play it! Simple enough, right? It's better than other tutorials that take you 10 years to finish!</text>
		<type>selection</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>5</id>
		<nextMessage>-1</nextMessage>
		<text>"What the hell was that opening music... seems like the only point of this game is this hot girl..."</text>
		<type>reply</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>20</id>
		<nextMessage>-1</nextMessage>
		<text>You may be thinking, "how the fuck am I supposed finish this game?!"</text>
		<type>normal</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>21</id>
		<nextMessage>-1</nextMessage>
		<text>Of course, isn't this the way that most mobile game companies makee their games these days?</text>
		<type>normal</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>22</id>
		<nextMessage>-1</nextMessage>
		<text>Simply kill 999999 enemies and reach level 100 to finish this game.</text>
		<type>normal</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>23</id>
		<nextMessage>40</nextMessage>
		<text>So you want to give up? Good, shut down your device, take a walk outside, take a deep breath...</text>
		<type>normal</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>40</id>
		<nextMessage>-1</nextMessage>
		<text>OR JUST PAY US TO WIN THIS GAME! TODAY'S SPECIAL DEAL: $99.99</text>
		<type>normal</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>24</id>
		<nextMessage>-1</nextMessage>
		<text>But, if you still want to continue, we can talk later. I'll be right back.</text>
		<type>normal</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>25</id>
		<nextMessage>-1</nextMessage>
		<text>When I first played these "epic" titles, I thought game developers were the gods of their worlds.</text>
		<type>normal</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>26</id>
		<nextMessage>-1</nextMessage>
		<text>After many years, I found myself wrong. The gods of these games are not our developers, but YOU! THE PLAYER!</text>
		<type>normal</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>27</id>
		<nextMessage>-1</nextMessage>
		<text>You complained that you don't have that much time to learn how to play, so we tried our best to make them as simply as we could.</text>
		<type>normal</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>28</id>
		<nextMessage>-1</nextMessage>
		<text>Then you said the controls were too complex! So we developed this gameplay with only one key. Now we can't even find a place to put a button for in-app purchases!</text>
		<type>normal</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>29</id>
		<nextMessage>-1</nextMessage>
		<text>You've heard of Pavlov's dog, right? If our game doesn't make players think, then what's the difference between dogs and players?</text>
		<type>normal</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>30</id>
		<nextMessage>-1</nextMessage>
		<text>SO NOW I KNOW THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT. PAY TO WIN. AREN'T YOU GRATEFUL?</text>
		<type>normal</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>31</id>
		<nextMessage>-1</nextMessage>
		<text>So, since you have played my awful game for this long already, I've decided to offer a little bit of help...</text>
		<type>normal</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>32</id>
		<nextMessage>-1</nextMessage>
		<text>GameController.Instance.Level = 100;</text>
		<type>normal</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>33</id>
		<nextMessage>-1</nextMessage>
		<text>Try using the QWER keys during your next playthrough (if there will be any).</text>
		<type>normal</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>7</id>
		<nextMessage>8</nextMessage>
		<text>Select:3</text>
		<type>normal</type>
	</message>
	<message>
		<id>8</id>
		<nextMessage>-1</nextMessage>
		<text>ALL DONE!</text>
		<type>reply</type>
	</message>
</messages>